Mohammad Jamal Malash

Address: Jenen, Palestine

Email: mohammadmalashcareer@gmail.com

Phone: +972 568961396

Objective

Bachelor's degree in Computer System Engineer and a React Native Developer. Possesses extensive experience in React Native, Redux, React Native Firebase, and React Hooks, with a strong background in state management and problem-solving. Successfully developed a real-time chat application utilizing Redux for state management and Firebase for authentication and cloud storage, and solved over 60+ problem on Leetcode and Code Forces.

Education

- 2019 2024: CSE (Computer System Engineering) student at Arab American University with a GPA of 3.44
- 2018- 2019: High school (Tawjihi), at Izzat Abu Al-Rub School, Scientific rout with a degree of 88.4

Experience

Graduation Project

Distributed modules for large landscape weather data collection the proposed system is proposed to span a wide geographical landscape, where module units communicate with other identical units to provide the required connectivity for data reporting used the Xbee Modules that works in Zigbee protocol and Arduin Uno for the unit, the program was written in C++.

React Native, HexaSol

Oct 2023 - Feb 2024

- 1. The position focuses on Mobile Development using **React-Native**.
- 2. Building Food-Delivery-App using React Native.
- 3. OOP concepts, and some best practice techniques.

React Native, Chat App

Feb 2023 – Mar 2024

Simple Chatting App using React Native and Firebase for a storage and authentication and redux as a state management library link for project documentation is on git hub: Chat-App.

Other Projects

- 1. A Basic Unit Testing Project in Python.
- 2. A unit testing for different cases for the factorial Function using pyTest framework.
- 3. Delivery App using Flutter.
- 4. All Projects in GitHub.

Skills

- **Programming Languages:** C/C++, Python, Java, JavaScript (JS/TS).
- Frameworks: React-native, flutter, Unittest in Python
- Databases: SQL, PL/SQL.
- Tools and Technologies: Git, windows, Linux.
- Project Management.
- Problem Solving.
- Marketing: Create Customer Value, segmentation, capture value,
- Communication Skills.

Activities

- Saturday 18 Mar 2023 Code Fighters Competition (4th Place)
- Monday 10 Oct 2022 ACM competition. (16th Place in the country)
- Thursday 24 Jun 2021 Be Solver competition (3rd Place).
- Projects in GitHub Mohammad-Jamal-Malash

Languages

• **Arabic** – Native Language.

• English – Very Good.

References

Dr. Tariq Zanon
AAUP/ Lecturer, Department of CSE
Contact Info:
tareq.zanoon@aaup.edu
+970 595 055 446

Prof. Osama Salameh
AAUP/ Lecturer Department of CSE
Contact Info:
osama.salameh@aaup.edu
+972 569 357 782